[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This plant has a long and colorful history and its legal status varies from country to country.", "correct_answer": "Cannabis", "incorrect_answers": ["Catnip", "Phalaris Grass", "Juniper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Box turtles are carnivores.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ok Im ending it with an easier question. What was unique about the day she killed everyone in 1979?", "correct_answer": "Jasons birthday", "incorrect_answers": ["friday the 13th", "the day Jason drowned", "her birthday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which animal is the record holder for the largest male genital organ-to-body length ratio in nature?", "correct_answer": "Slug", "incorrect_answers": ["Starfish", "Horse", "Elephant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These animals are the subject of study of coleopterology, which is a subfield of entomology.", "correct_answer": "beetles", "incorrect_answers": ["jaguars", "tigers", "snakes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Eight years before George Washington was elected  President of the USA, this politician was appointed President of the United States by the Continental Congress.", "correct_answer": "Thomas McKean", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry Lightfoot Lee", "Samuel Adams", "John Hancock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the musical performed by Frederick and the monster in the film Young Frankenstein?", "correct_answer": "Puttin on The Ritz", "incorrect_answers": ["Its Alive!", "Frau Blucher", "My Name is Frankenstein!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lories and lorikeets have special tongues with brush-like tips for feeding on very small insects.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the microscope holds the draw tube in place?", "correct_answer": "Body tube", "incorrect_answers": ["Base", "Arm", "Stage clip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "POP is used to retrieve e-mail from a mail server.", "correct_answer": "Post Office Protocol", "incorrect_answers": ["Performance Oriented Packaging", "Primary Outgoing Protocol", "Post Office Procedures"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color goldfish were most prized by the Chinese royalty several centuries ago?", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Silver", "Orange", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Adult Goliath beetles, found in Africas tropical forests, feed on what?", "correct_answer": "Fruits and tree sap", "incorrect_answers": ["Leaves and grasses", "Insects and other invertebrates", "Carrion"]}]